Guide to the Spyros P. Skouras Papers M0509
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 9: Speeches
  - Motion Picture Industry 1953
    - Report To The Stockholders By SPS, 1953 May 19 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Notes On Special Meeting Of Executives & Department Heads, 1953 May 21 (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - SPS speech in Germany, 1953 June 9 (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Remarks By SPS At Cinemascope Demonstration - London, 1953 June 29 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - RCA Sales Organization Meeting, 1953 Aug 14 (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Boston Allied Convention Cinemascope, 1953 Oct (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Convention Speech, 1953 Oct 8 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Testimonial dinner honoring Al Lichtman, 1953 Oct 8 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1954
    - Speech To London Exhibitors, 1954 Feb 10 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - SPS Speech To Screen Writers Club, 1954 Feb 21 (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Remarks Of SPS At Plaza Luncheon, 1954 March 28 (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Exhibitors Forum, 1954 May 6 (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Address By SPS At Annual Stockholders V Meeting, 1954 May 18 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Speech To TOA Luncheon, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Speech Made By SPS On European Trip (France, Germany, England), 1954 Nov 22, Dec 29 (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Cinemascope, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - Home Television, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - Producers Luncheon - Mexico Trip, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - Re: Stereophonic Sound To Be Used In Presentation Of Cinemascope Pictures, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - SPS "Will Television Kill The Cinema", 1954 (Box 80, Folder 40)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1955
    - Speech For Producers Luncheon, 1955 May 26 (Box 80, Folder 41)
    - Fox Meeting, 1955 June 18 (Box 80, Folder 42)
    - Meeting National Allied Theatre Owners Assn, Chicago, 1955 Nov 7 (Box 80, Folder 43)
    - Introduction For Recording To Albert Cornfield, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 44)
    - Suggested Recordings By SPS Introduced By Emanuel Silverstone & Les Whelan, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 45)
    - Suggested Speech As.Dictated By SPS, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 46)
    - Recorded Address By SPS, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 47)
    - Speech For Drive-In Theatre Owners, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 48)
    - Dividend Report, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 49)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1956
    - Sales Convention, 1956 Jan 7 (Box 80, Folder 50)
    - Annual Stockholders Meeting, 1956 May 15 (Box 80, Folder 51)
    - Stockholders Meeting, 1956 May 15 (Box 80, Folder 52)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1957
    - Stockholders Meeting, 1957 May 21 (Box 80, Folder 53)
    - Stockholders Speech, 1957 May 21 (Box 80, Folder 54)
    - SPS Opening Speech For Opening L.A. Conference, 1957 Dec (Box 80, Folder 55)
    - Address By SPS For Film To Be Titled "Forward With 20th Century Fox", 1957 (Box 80, Folder 56)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1958
    - The Screen Producers Guild - SPS Received The "Milestone Award,", 1958 April 13 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Annual Stockholders Meeting, 1958 May 20 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Stockholders Meeting, 1958 May 20 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Luncheon Of The Motion Picture Council Of The District Of Columbia, Wash. D.C., 1958 Jun 30 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Sales Managers Advertising Heads Executive Of 20th Century Fox, 1958 July 15 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Luncheon Given For The Air Force On The Occasion Of The Premiere "The Hunters,", 1958 Aug 26 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Dinner At Des Moines On The Occasion Of Abe H. Blank's 50th Anniversary In Show Business, 1958 Sep 12 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Chicago Convention Of Exhibitors Toll Television, Chicago, 1958 Oct 15 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Convention Of Exhibitors TOA, Miami, 1958 Oct 22 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Honoring Ed Lomba, 1958 Nov 11 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Speech At Exhibitors Meeting, 1958 Nov 14 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Testimonial Luncheon To Boy Coyne, 1958 Dec 11 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1959
    - Speech For annual Studio Meeting, 1959 Jan 12 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Speech For Studio Meeting, 1959 Jan 13 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Opening Of The National Convention Of The Sales Dept., 1959 March 15 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Annual Stockholders Meeting, 1959 May 19 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - U.S. Exhibit In Moscow, 1959 Aug 5 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Statement By 5p~1 Vienna, Austria, 1959 Aug 12 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Film Industry SPS Speech, 1959 Aug 25 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Domestic Sales Meeting, 1959 Sep 1 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Sales & Exploitation Meeting, 1959 Sep 2 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Sales Meeting, 1959 Dec 31 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1960
    - Sales Meeting, 1960 Jan 8 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Speeches For Meetings On West Coast Re: Writers' Strike, 1960 Jan (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - "Sales Meeting" Opening Speech, 1960 Jan 6 (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Annual Stockholders Meeting, 1960 May 17 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Special Stockholders Meeting, 1960 Oct 17 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1961
    - SPS Address At Meeting With Studio, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Executives, 1961 Feb 23 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Annual Stockholders Meeting, 1961 May 16 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Award Presented To SPS For Service To Industry - Assoc. Motion Picture Advertisement, 1961 Oct 26 (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Miami Speech - Allied States Association Of Motion Picture Exhibitors, 1961 Dec 6 (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1962
    - Tape Recording, 1962 Feb 23 (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - United Theatre Owners Of The Heart Of America, Kansas City, 1962 March 6 (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - Motion Picture Industry Honoring SPS, 1962 April 10 (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - 20th Anniversary SPS Speech, 1962 April 12 (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - Stockholders Meeting, 1962 May 15 (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Fox Meeting, 1962 June 27 (Box 81, Folder 37)
    - 20th Annual Convention Of The Theatre Owners Assoc. Of S. Carolina, 1962 Sep 25 (Box 81, Folder 38)
    - 1962 Motion Picture Amusement Division Of Joint Defense Appeal - SPS Award,., 1962 Oct 25 (Box 81, Folder 39)
    - SPS Speech TOA Convention, Miami, 1962 Nov 10 (Box 81, Folder 40)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1963
    - Testimonial Dinner - Honoring Frank Freeman, Beverly Hills, 1963 April 28 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Banquet Of The Allied Theatre Owners Of Wisconsin Annual Convention, Milwaukee, 1963 Sep 25 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Introducing DFZ Honored Guest And Speaker At The TOA Luncheon, 1963 Oct 29 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1965 - 1970
    - All Industry Testimonial Dinner Honoring Jack Lorentz Upon His Retirement, 1965 July 21 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - NATO Walt Disney Memorial Award To SPS, 1968 Nov 14 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Larchmont Mamaroneck Motion Picture Council, 1970 May 1 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - (Filmed) Henry Klinger, 1970 July 21 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Motion Picture Industry - Unidentified And Undated
    - Motion Picture Industry - Unidentified And Undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Various 1948
    - Conference Of Christians & Jews Luncheon, 1948 Jan 6 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - American: Overseas aid & UN Appeal For Children, 1948 Jan 16 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - American Overseas Aid. Luncheon, 1948 Feb 13 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Brotherhood Week Dinner, L.A., 1948 Feb 24 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - American Overseas Aid Luncheon, 1948 March 8 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Trustees Luncheon -. Boston University, 1948 March 12 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Accepting Honor From Boston University, 1948 March 12 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Anterican Overseas Aid United Nations Appeal For Children, 1948 March 15 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - American Overseas Aid Appeal, 1948 April 23 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Testimonial To Oscar Hammerstein & Dick Rodgers, 1948 April 28 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - American Overseas Aid UN Appeal For Children, 1948 May 25 (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Testimonial Dinner to Andy Smith, 1948 May 26 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Speech By SPS At Station WLIB, 1948 July 4 (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - Remarks By SPS Introducing Dwight D. Eisenhower At UN Appeal, 1948 July 8 (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Gus Eyssell testimonial, 1948 Oct 14 (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - United Jewish Appeal Luncheon For SPS, 1948 Nov 24 (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - Palestinian Fund Dinner, 1948 Dec 7 (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - B'nai B'r1th Dinner In Honor Of D. Zanuck, 1948 Dec 13 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Various 1949
    - Press Conference On SPS Return From Trip To Greece, 1949 Feb (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Luncheon Of American Red Cross, 1949 March 1 (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - American Hellenic Chamber Of Commerce, 1949 March 4 (Box 82, Folder 29)
    - Overseas Press Club Luncheon, 1949 March 16 (Box 82, Folder 30)
    - Speech For Cathedral, 1949 March 27 (Box 82, Folder 31)
    - Hellenic University Club, 1949 March 28 (Box 82, Folder 32)
    - Cocktail Party Meeting In Preparation For Milton Berle Dinner, 1949 March 31 (Box 82, Folder 33)
    - Citation To Si Fabian Joint Defense Appeal Of The American Jewish Comm., 1949 April 7 (Box 82, Folder 34)
    - Thank You Dinner Greek Independence Celebration, 1949 May 3 (Box 82, Folder 35)
    - Testimonial Dinner For Milton Berle, 1949 May 12 (Box 82, Folder 36)
    - NY Society Of Security Analysts (Little Theatre), 1949 May 25 (Box 82, Folder 37)
    - Dinner Under Auspices Of Chamber Of Commerce Commemorating St. Louis Week, 1949 Sep 15 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Oren Root Dinner, 1949 Oct 18 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - United Jewish Appeal, 1949 Nov 25 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - American Fund For Israel Institutions, 1949 Nov 30 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Address By SPS Before The Leadership Conference Of The U.S. Jewish Appeal, 1949 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Various 1950
    - Red Cross Dinner For George C. Marshall, 1950 Jan 17 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Air Force Assoc. Luncheon "12 Olciock High,", 1950 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - United Jewish Appeal Miami, 1950 Feb 26 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Boston Jubilee Comm. And Boston University Speech, 1950 May 18 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Brotherhood Conference Unesco House, Paris, 1950 June 8 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Brotherhood & Teamwork For European Prosperity, Paris, 1950 June 9 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Statement By SPS On Return From Europe, 1950 June 25 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - United Jewish Appeal Meeting, Boston, 1950 Sep 27 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Dinner Honoring General James Van Fleet, 1950 Oct 5 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - World Brotherhood Extension Committee Opening Meeting, Wash. D.C., 1950 Nov 9 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Extension Committee For World Brotherhood Private Dinner Board Members, 1950 Nov 9 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Greek Orthodox Churches In America, St. Louis, 1950 Nov 28 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Various 1951
    - American Fund For Israel Institutions, 1951 Jan 8 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Red Cross Luncheon, 1951 Feb 5 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Children To Palestine Dinner, 1951 April 4 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - United Church Women Speech Made By Mr. Bell in Absence Of SPS, 1951 Nov 15 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Various 1952
    - National Conference Of Christians and Jews Brotherhood.. Dinner, 1952 Jan 9 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Israel Bond Drive Luncheon, 1952 Jan 14 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Red Cross Luncheon Motionpicture Division, 1952 Feb 14 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Ahepa Banquet, 1952 March 24 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Baseball Writers Dinner, 1952 April 12 (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - Luncheon Given By T.J. Watson Honoring C. Nikolopoulos, Mayor of Athens, 1952 May 13 (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Luncheon For The Committee Of The Armed Execs, 1952 June 17 (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - 3-1/2 Minute Talk On The Importance Of Registering & Voting, 1952 Sep 10 (Box 83, Folder 29)
    - Voice Of America Broadcast - Seoul, Korea, 1952 Oct 14 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Various 1953
    - Welcome Home Dinner, 1953 Jan 6 (Box 83, Folder 31)
    - American Fund For Israel Institutions In Honor Of Sol Hurok, 1953 Jan8 (Box 83, Folder 32)
    - Luncheon Honoring General James Van Fleet, 1953 April 24 (Box 83, Folder 33)
    - Luncheon Benefit American Korean Foundation, 1953 April 28 (Box 83, Folder 34)
    - Remarks By SPS At Dinner Of Spyros Markeninis, 1953 May 31 (Box 83, Folder 35)
    - Draft Speech 25th Anniversary Dinner National Conference Of Christians And Jews, 1953 Oct 21 (Box 83, Folder 36)
  - Various 1954
    - Honoring The President Of Turkey, 1954 Feb 1 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Hellenic Chamber Of Commerce Dinner, 1954 March 5 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Red Cross Luncheon, 1954 March 30 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Testimonial Dinner Held In The Emerson.Hotel Tendered By The Variety Club, Baltimore, 1954 Mar 31 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Variety Club, Baltimore, 1954 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Elian Dinner Meeting, 1954 May 12 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - United Jewish Appeal Luncheon Presentation Of Hebrew Bible To SPS, 1954 May 20 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - New York Medical College, 1954 June 2 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - "Flight Of The White Heron" Screening, 1954 June 16 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Ernest Turnbull Dinner, 1954 June 28 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - White House Luncheon, 1954 June 29 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Dinner In Honor Of Ambassador Clare Booth Luce, 1954 July 28 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - AMVETS, Miami, Florida, 1954 Aug 28 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Text Of Speech To Be Delivered By SPS Jr. (Assoc. Of Scholars Of The Anglo-American), 1954 Sep 9 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Inter-Faith Rally, 1954 Sep 26 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Stephanopoulos Dinner, 1954 Oct 1 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Homecoming For Si Fabian, 1954 Oct 13 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - Independent Citizens Committee, 1954 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Speech Of Welcome To The King & Queen Of Greece, 1954 Nov 2 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Paramount Luncheon For Their Majesties King And Queen Of Greece, 1954 Nov 13 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Various 1955
    - American Fund For Israel Institution Dinner, 1955 Jan 5 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Red Cross Luncheon, 1955 March 1 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Red Cross Speech, 1955 March 1 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Greek Refugee Problem, 1955 March 16 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Greek Refugee Problem, 1955 May 7 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - Variety Clubs International, 1955 May 7 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - University Speech (Mexican), 1955 May 30 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - New York Medical College Dinner, 1955 June 2 (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - World Brotherhood, 1955 July (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Various 1956
    - Dinner Honoring Senator Capehart, 1956 Jan 4 (Box 84, Folder 30)
    - Red Cross Speech, 1956 Feb 29 (Box 84, Folder 31)
    - Greek Independence, 1956 March 25 (Box 84, Folder 32)
    - Clergy-Laity Congress, 1956 Oct 17 (Box 84, Folder 33)
    - Brandeis University Speech, 1956 Oct 31 (Box 84, Folder 34)
  - Various 1957
    - American Fund For Israel Institutions, 1957 Jan 7 (Box 84, Folder 35)
    - Brotherhood Luncheon, 1957 March 28 (Box 84, Folder 36)
    - Hadassah Dinner, 1957 June 18 (Box 84, Folder 37)
    - International: Cultural Center For Youth, 1957 Nov 6 (Box 84, Folder 38)
    - World Brotherhood Luncheon, 1957 Nov 12 (Box 84, Folder 39)
  - Various 1958
    - March Of Dimes Jack Warner Dinner, 1958 Feb 26 (Box 84, Folder 40)
    - Festa Di Gala Italiana, 1958 Nov 5 (Box 84, Folder 41)
    - The Royal Naval Film Corp., 1958 Nov 19 (Box 84, Folder 42)
  - Various 1959
    - Conrad Hi1ton Testimonial Dinner, 1959 Jan 14 (Box 84, Folder 43)
    - Red Cross Campaign, 1959 March 10 (Box 84, Folder 44)
    - On Visit To Russia, 1959 July 15 (Box 84, Folder 45)
    - Colony Club Russian Visitors, 1959 Aug 19 (Box 84, Folder 46)
    - Russian trip, 1959 Aug 21 (Box 84, Folder 47)
    - 20th Century Fox Studio Luncheon Honoring Nikita. Khruschev, 1959 Sep 19 (Box 84, Folder 48)
    - Luncheon Honoring E. Adnan Menders, Prime Minister Of Turkey, 1959 Oct 19 (Box 84, Folder 49)
    - American Fund For Israel Institutions, 1959 Oct 23 (Box 84, Folder 50)
  - Various 1960
    - American Israel Cultural Foundation Dinner, 1960 Jan 6 (Box 84, Folder 51)
    - Hellenic University Foundation, 1960 Jan 8 (Box 84, Folder 52)
    - Northern California Committee For Refugees Dinner, 1960 Feb 29 (Box 84, Folder 53)
    - Remarks By SPS For Variety Clubs Convention, Toronto, 1960 June (Box 84, Folder 54)
    - Dr. Dooley Tribute Dinner, 1960 July 23 (Box 84, Folder 55)
    - Luncheon For Sarwat Okasha, 1960 Sep 29 (Box 84, Folder 56)
    - Breakfast Meeting For Richard Nixon And Cabot Lodge, 1960 Oct 5 (Box 84, Folder 57)
  - Various 1961
    - Luncheon For George V. Allen, 1961 Jan 25 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - March Of Dimes Dinner In Honor Of Bob Hope, 1961 March 3 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Red Cross luncheon, 1961 March 9 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Internationial Cultural For Youth In Jerusalem, 1961 Nov 8 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Various 1962
    - Cathedral Ball, 1962 Feb 16 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - March Of Dimes Honoring George Jessel, 1962 Feb (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - March Of Dimes Humanitarian Award, 1962 Feb 27 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Red Cross Luncheon, 1962 March 20 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Memorial Concert For Mitropooulos, 1962 April 1 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - All American Committee For Rockefeller, 1962 Oct 18 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Musicians Aid Society, 1962 Nov 1 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - American Israel Cultural Foundation, 1962 Nov 27 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Various 1963
    - Holy Cross Theological Seminary, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Celebration Of WNEW 30th Anniversary For The Musicians Aid Society, 1963 July 24 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Luncheon For Dr. Mohamed Younes, 1963 Sep 19 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - U.S. Committee For Refugees, 1963 Nov 1 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Various 1964
    - Republican "Go-Day" Dinner, 1964 Jan 29 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Speech for The Archbishop's Dinner, 1964 Feb 25 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Meeting Of The Young Adults Of The Archdiocesan Cathedral, 1964 March 4 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Cathedral Meeting, 1964 March 31 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Dinner Given Inv:Honr Of Professor N. Christeas., 1964 May 12 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Annual Cathedral Dinner Dance, 1964 May 15 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - D-Day Commemorative Committee 20th Anniversary Luncheon, 1964 June 6 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Papandreou Dinner, 1964 June 26 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Clergy-Laity 17th Biennial Congress In Denver, Colo., 1964 July 1 (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Radio Broadcast Endorsing LBJ, 1964 Oct 27 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Various 1965
    - Annual Cathedral Dinner Dance, 11-Feb (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - Annual "Salute To Youth" Rally, May 7 (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - Graduation Exercises Of The Cathedral School, June 16 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - Launching Of The Sea Jet - Maryland, 2-Sep (Box 85, Folder 30)
    - Consecration Of Saints Constantine & Helen Church, 3-Oct (Box 85, Folder 31)
    - Eisenhower 75th Birthday Dinner, 14-Oct (Box 85, Folder 32)
    - Circus Of Saints And Sinners Luncheon, 19-Oct (Box 85, Folder 33)
    - "Oxi" Greek Celebration, 29-Oct (Box 85, Folder 34)
    - Archbishop Lakovos (Box 85, Folder 35)
    - Dinner Honoring Jack Lorentz (Box 85, Folder 36)
    - St. Paul's Society Breakfast Honoring SPS (Box 85, Folder 37)
  - Various 1966
    - Annual Cathedral Ball, 1966 Feb 10 (Box 85, Folder 38)
    - Cocktail Meeting For Mary Macarthur Award Dinner, 1966 April 13 (Box 85, Folder 39)
    - B'nai B'rith Tribute Dinner To Richard Rodgers, 1966 May 17 (Box 85, Folder 40)
    - St. Moritz Meeting Of The UGOC, 1966 May 26 (Box 85, Folder 41)
    - Award of Honorary Degree Of Doctor Of Human Letters To SPS, University Of Tampa, 1966 Junes 15 (Box 85, Folder 42)
    - Graduation Exercises Of The Cathedral School, 1966 June 15 (Box 85, Folder 43)
    - Speech At Clergy-Laity Congress, Montreal, Canada, 1966 June 27 (Box 85, Folder 44)
    - National Services, 1966 Sep 16 (Box 85, Folder 45)
    - Cocktail Party Given By SPS For Governor Rockefeller, 1966 Oct 24 (Box 85, Folder 46)
  - Various 1967
    - "Education & The Motion Picture Industry" Presented By SPS At University Of Tampa, 1967 Jan 9 (Box 85, Folder 47)
    - Salvation Army, 1967 March 3 (Box 85, Folder 48)
    - "Man Of The Year" Award To SPS By The Boys Club Of Queens, 1967 June 7 (Box 85, Folder 50)
    - The Members Of The Graduating Class Of The Cathedral. School, 1967 June 14 (Box 85, Folder 51)
    - Luncheon Of American Turkish ~ Society, 1967 June 30 (Box 85, Folder 52)
    - Tribute Dinner To Father Basil Gregory, 1967 June 26 (Box 85, Folder 53)
    - UGOC Speech, C1eveland, Ohio, 1967 July 7 (Box 85, Folder 54)
    - UGOC Speech, Baltimore, 1967 Sep 9 (Box 85, Folder 55)
    - Archbishops Nameday Dinner, 1967 Oct 2 (Box 85, Folder 56)
    - Variety Clubs Dinner In Honor Of Ralph Pries, Philadelphia, 1967 Dec 6 (Box 85, Folder 57)
  - Various 1968
    - Notes For SPS At Chapter (UGOC) Formation Meeting, Boston, 1968 Feb 21 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Variety Clubs Convention, Honolulu, 1968 May 6 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Variety Clubs International Convention, Los Angeles, 1968 May 29 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Annual Board Of Governors Meeting UGOC, Brookline, Mass., 1968 June 1 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Variety Tent V #35 Luncheon Honoring SPS, 1968 June 11 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - The March Of Dimes Humanitarian Award to Leo Jaffe, 1968 June 12 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Cathedral Graduation, 1968 June 13 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Remarks Of SPS At Dedication Ceremonies Center For Russian Jewry, 1968 June 26 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Church-Laity Congress, Athens, Greece, 1968 July (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - The Communications Forum - The Center Of American Living, 1968 Sep 17 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Variety, St. Louis, 1968 Oct 31 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - "Padeja Award" Hellenic University Club, 1968 Nov 2 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - "Walt Disney Memorial Award" To SPS, San Francisco, 1968 Nov 14 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Variety Clubs, Louisville, Kentucky, 1968 Nov 16 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Variety Clubs, Minneapolis, Minn., 1968 Nov 29 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Variety Club Celebrity Ball, 1968 Dec 2 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Morality in Media Award To SPS, 1968 Dec 9 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Various 1969
    - SPS 75th Jubilee dinner, 1969 Jan 28 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Testimonial Dinner Judge Nicholas Tsoucalas, 1969 Feb 1 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Variety Clubs, L.A., 1969 March 13 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - B'nai B'rith Cinema Lodge Award To SPS, 1969 April 24 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Intl. Variety Club Luncheon St The Beverly Hilton, L.A., 1969 May 30 (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - Suggested Remarks For Chicago UGOC, 1969 June 20-2l (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - Remarks For Cocktail Meeting "The Arrangement,", 1969 Sep 23 (Box 86, Folder 24)
    - Edison Foundation, Detroit, Mich., 1969 Oct 21 (Box 86, Folder 25)
    - "The Arrangement" Premiere, 1969 Nov 18 (Box 86, Folder 26)
    - Actors Youth Fund, 1969 Dec 3 (Box 86, Folder 27)
    - Morality In The Media Award To Ed Sullivan, 1969 Dec 8 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Various 1970
    - Hellenic University Club "Padeia Award" To Nicholas Angleton, 1970 Jan 30 (Box 86, Folder 29)
    - UGOC Honoring General Van Fleet, 1970 May 17 (Box 86, Folder 30)
    - Boys Club Of. Queens Honoring Salah Hassanein, 1970 June 3 (Box 86, Folder 31)
    - Dinner Honoring Father Contos - Natl. Conference Of Christians and Jews, 1970 June 8 (Box 86, Folder 32)
    - American Israel Chamber Of Commerce Honoring SPS, 1970 June 24 (Box 86, Folder 33)
    - Goya Pi1gramage to Statue Of Liberty, 1970 July l (Box 86, Folder 34)
    - Ethnic Group Dinner For Gov. Rockefeller, 1970 Oct 15 (Box 86, Folder 35)
    - Archbishop Iakovos Dinner, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 36)
    - Iakovos Dinner, 1970 Oct 30 (Box 86, Folder 37)